Good evening. I hope you can see me.
Wow, it's a little skewed.
Good evening.
I'm Kumi Sasaki, captain of the 46 hairballs.
Today, we've gathered here for a gyoza party.
But right off the bat, I think they're a little skewed.
How about it? What do you think?
Good evening.
I can see the comments here.
A dumpling party!
Yay!
Well, this dumpling party is...
I love gyoza so much.
I love gyoza even more, and it's my favorite dish!
On the 1st anniversary of Minato-zaka-46's debut
I held a live distribution of the gyoza party
I think it was 3 years ago.
That was about 3 years ago.
At that time
I've got a YouTube channel now.
I came back.
We're going to have a live distribution party. We're going to have a live dumpling party.
I can already hear knocking.
Is someone coming today?
Yes. Good evening.
They're here. Good evening.
I can't see you. - Good evening.
Who is it? Who is it?
Who is it? Maybe it's better that way.
I'm a lot of things. Wow, that's great.
I haven't shown you that in a while.
It's all wrapped up.
Oh, he's here. He's here.
Good evening. Good evening.
It's Konoka Matsuda.
Konoka Matsuda, the other day...
The other day... Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Not at all.
Small talk. Small talk.
What's that thing you're holding?
You know, the one I was telling you about.
You know, the one? You know, the one you've been dreaming about?
You know, the one you've been longing for.
What? She brought the perfect ingredients for gyoza.
I heard it's a gyoza party, so I brought some pretty solid ingredients.
Wow, big, shiny black trash bag!
It's high-end.
Amazing!
TEREN!
Wow!
Can you tell?
It says "YouTube.
This is it, John!
Well, since you're the captain, please open this.
What? You don't mind?
Yes, I brought this.
What? It's surprisingly light.
Yes, it is, indeed.
Then let's do it together.
Where did you get this?
Oh, here.
Here we go. Do you guys get it?
I want you all to do this one movement in front of the screen. Ready!
Oh, wow! Wow!
We're in sync. Wow! It's all on this vinyl. It says "Hinatazaka Channel" on it.
Maybe we should get a closer look at the camera. Yes, I'll take it out of the plastic. You're taking it out of the vinyl?
Yes, out of the vinyl. It looks like this.
Oh, really. In English. Recognize your team.
Recognize your team. Ah, ta-da! Amazing!
Oh, it's me. Yoo-hoo! I got a notification.
Wow! Please take a look.
Presents and Hinatasaka Channel
Passing 10
100,000 subscribers!
We got it! It was pretty solid really. Thank you very much. You brought this? Yes, I did.
It's a bit of a waste to use it as a tool. Indeed. That's right. I guess I'll put it on display. Decorate it.
Let's chew on it. Certainly. I'll chew it while looking at it. Let's eat dumplings while looking at this.
You're going to eat it while watching this? No way.
I'm so happy. Do you want to decorate it? Yes, I think so. Do you think it will look good on the shelf behind it? Do you want to adjust the angle of view? I don't know.
It's really self-serve, my self-serve.
If I set it like this, it looks good.
It looks good.
Yes.
My sense of touch. My sense of touch.
Please stop.
I want to see it.
It's kinda, you know, nice. It's pretty good. It looks good.
I can see the comments, you know. Can you turn off the comment on Kumi's face?
Oh, no chat. Oh, I got it. I'm looking at it over here. I see everyone's comments.
Well, since we're here... Oh! You're a gourmet? Since you're here, try Kumi's dumplings.
Kero? Is that a Kumi word? Kero? Eat me. Please take a look. Just in advance.
Oh, I slipped. Oh, hey. Slip dumplings. They're slip dumplings.
I prepared them in advance. It's nice.
I hope you can watch it with me over dinner or something. That's right.
Let's bake them a little at a time.
Are you warm?
Are you guys warm?
Are you warm?Are you warm?
Do you want to lay down some nection?
Sure thing. Thank you very much.
You're very kind.
That's why you're the captain.
You all came, you know.
I already arrived sluggishly to eat a lot.
The kind you can tell when you're dusty.
I dressed in clothes that are not constrictive.
I might be sleeping here around here.
It's Kono's at home.
Konochan is shaped like this.
What? Please don't tell me.
Oh, sorry.
I've been to your house.
I have Kumi's house too.
Shall we go there once?
Yes, I do. Sorry.
Lay the oil on the floor. You're the timekeeper.
I can't push it today. We have a lot of members coming in.
Is that so? Is that so? But it might be a lie.
It might be a lie. It might be a lie, but I thought if we called it a party, a lot of people would come.
There are people who like to party. People who like to party.
It would be a waste if they don't come. But it's a party when the sun is there too.
Indeed, it already is. How many do you want to eat?
How many can I eat? As many as you want. I made a lot.
About five? About 3 or 4.
Then let's make 6. Shall we eat them in threes?
No, 2 or 4. Which is 2 or 4?
That would be Ono-chan. Isn't she the one who is popular with the ladies?
So it's 2 or 4. Because I was hungry.
Vertically. Do you eat more than your seniors?
No, not at all. The group read it.
That's it. It would be terrible if they cut it out.
Like this. I'll show you the point.
It's true that the baking part is not shown at all. It's difficult.
But it's difficult when you're alone. One time.
I'm getting comments.
It's difficult. Like this. Yu also wants to eat five dumplings.
Eat them. That's good.
I've got some practice baking. If we move them to this side...
It might make it easier to see.
I've been thinking about that. You think so?
Oh, what? There's something in the back of the picture. What?
Behind Kumi-san.
Ah, what is it?
What is it? Please tell me.
It's something.
What is it?
Huh?
Was it kitchen paper? Oh, I knew it. I thought I was looking at the wrong thing.
What is it? What is it? It sounded like Velcro. Today.
What's that? The back side is covered like this.
It's cute. This is Gyojon Nathan.
I saw this on your blog. Did you buy it?
I bought it for a Halloween costume.
I like gyoza. That's why. It's interesting.
It's amazing. It's like a gyoza is cooking gyoza. Are you okay with eating with friends?
We don't have that kind of concept. Gyoza is just for being eaten. You have to be eaten.
I see. So this is an assortment of gyoza you have eaten.
It contains an assortment of my thoughts on gyoza.
Is it okay if I don't put water in this? Yes. I'll add potato starch.
It's getting a little baked, so I think it would be better to add a little more water. I see.
Oh, I see.
Are you okay? Your arms are a little tight.
Actually, I thought it was a little tight, but it's an important point.
But when it burns, I can just swing it to the side by myself.
But here, it doesn't have enough weight.
I'll make sure it's firm.
Thank you.
Yes, I'm fine.
No problem at all.
Oh!
That's great!
I'll leave it to you.
I'm a little nervous about having everyone eat it.
Ah, but I understand. I know that feeling.
I've never done it before.
You don't understand. I understand.
I understand. I've never experienced it.
I understand what it's like to be a family member.
Yes, family is nothing at all.
There is a stable, normal taste.
It's a taste that we grew up with.
Every family is different. I'm sure.
Do you want some tea?
Is that okay?
Yes, I do.
I'm glad to hear it.
We have green tea and oolong tea.
Green tea then.
Okay.
Wow, 333,000 people are watching.
Is that a lot of people?
That's right.
Thank you very much.
Many dumplings.
Dumplings.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I eat so much.I eat so much.
Don't mind it.
I should care.
Looks delicious.
Huh? Don't you want to cheer?
I'll do cheerleading. I'll do cheerleading, too.
You don't mind? You can have it.
I'll do it.
Let me sit down.
That's great. Next time, take care of it and make a new joint.
Thank you. I'm glad you feel that way.
Cheers!
That's great. I like it. This kind of loose delivery.
It's good. The cup is big. It's a small face effect.
Small face effect right away.
It's about time. It might be good.
Oh no, it's on the cord.
I wonder if it's cooked all the way through.
I'll get the plates ready.
I'm a little nervous right now because it's our first customer.
Not at all. Shall I put it here?
Okay, let's go.
Three, two, one.
The wings are really tight.
Ah!
Oh! That's great!
The firepower is a little bit...
But it's great.
It's good.
They're practicing in detention.
It turned out great. It's great! Looks delicious.
Here you go, Komin. Here you go.
Sorry for the big plate.
I'll loosen it once.
I think I'll bake the next one.
Sure thing.
How long has this been cooking?
Oh, but it's already been 14 minutes.
No way.
I have to go home.
That was fast.
I'm leaving.
No, it's not that I don't want to go home.
That's for sure.
Then I'll stay here like this.
Where it won't show.
Sometimes..,
I look through the silver lining like this, this way.
I move to the silver vertical reflection, then to the reflection, then to the other side, and then, what? And then, what?
That's not good.
Oh, that's right. What do you put on it?
I recommend ponzu.
Okay, I'll go with your recommendation, ponzu.
Shall we?
Yes, please.
This is self-service.
Yes.
Self-serve.
Oh, sorry.
It's my first time opening it.
Don't worry. Three minutes to three minutes.
A party is something that everyone makes together.
Oh, why do you say that? I love it.
I love it too.
They called me well-done. Well-done, indeed.
We don't have steak.
Oh, I'm glad we're having it, too. I'm glad we're having it together.
I miss it. We used to do it like this.
This Kumi's.
Inokori dumplings.
This way.
They were finished with grilled verdant.
Oh, wow!
Delicious!
It's delicious!
Bon appétit!
Mmm.
It was Matsuda.
Here it is!
Matsuda!
I'm so happy.
It's delicious.
Really?
It's good.
The meat is firm and the skin is firm too.
Yes, it is. A little thicker skin.
The last time I had it, it was probably thinner, but it was a little thicker.
It was 3 years ago, so I don't remember much from that time.
It's true, but it's delicious. I'm allowed to do it with the crust.
It's delicious.
Oh, it's delicious.
Is it good? I'm glad.
I'm most happy when people say it's delicious.
I want everyone to have a delicious meal.
Mom?
I'm your mother.
I am Hinata's mother.I am the mother of the sun.
But I think he's my father.
Isn't he Hyuga's Gifu?
That's for sure.
You think of me as your father?
Yes, I do.
I thought so myself.
You certainly have a lot of manly qualities.
I don't really tell everyone what to do,
I don't really tell everyone what to do.
I like to play with them.
I want to be kissed.
I'm just putting this on.
I'm sorry.
You look so cute right now.
My one word of determination.
Can I ask you one more time?
I wish I could be kissed like that. All the time.
My mouth canceled it.
Good. Good.
I want to be kissed goodbye.
I'm not soft.
He cares a lot about time and angle of view.
No, no, no.
I did my time today.
That's right.
It's just a little bit of time.
We've done our time.
That's right, it's time.
After all, I can't see the dumplings here.
Maybe I should move it away a little more.
Sure.
Which is better?
I'd like to hear your comments,
What kind of face do you want to see in the project?
I'd like to see some dumplings.
I'd like to see the vertical,
I thought of putting them on the sofa.
I thought of that.
Just once,
You're a genius!
Which one?
Whose voice is that?
You're a genius!
I'll be your coordinator.
Please do.
Back up a little bit,
Back up, back up, back up.
This is hard. How do we get back?
Come on!
You know?
What?
Hamaji.
Yes, I know.
I met him the first time.
Marco's.
That's good, that's good, that's good, that's good.
This is the first time I met someone to do this with.
What?
That's good.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
It's good, right?
It's getting a little, uh, long.
A little bit longer.
I'm doing a little trial and error on this one.
Just a little bit.
Oh, how's that? Like this?
Oh, yes, yes.
It's good.
Oh, good, good, good.
Oh, it's good, it's good.
Just the gyoza. It's terrible.
No way!
You might be a gyoza fan!
Oh, I see
I don't know Hinatazaka.
but with the hashtag gyoza
I don't know about the hashtag "gyoza", but you might be one of the people who are following me.
Thank you very much.
I'm in a group called Hyugaizaka46.
Yes, that's right.
Please eat a lot of these.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Welcome.
Oh!
Oh, no!
I'm so happy.
Hello.
Excuse me
Hello, hello.
Well, well, well
Well, well, well...
I wonder if you can recognize my voice.
Hello. - Hello.
Good evening.
Good evening.Good evening.
You've lowered your voice.
He's cute.
Come here, boy.
Come on in.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
I brought you something.
Oh, I'm so happy.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Oh, he's here.
Scary.
I'm Hariwa Yamaguchi.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Good evening.
I'm Marii Morimoto.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm so happy to meet you.
Thank you.
That's great.
Oh, wow!
I just burned it.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
Look at this!
We brought a bunch of them!
Oh, they're so cute!
So cute!
Bon appétit!
Souvenirs!
Here's a peach
The face
Lower half of the face
Wow!
This way.
Chocolate?
I like sweets.
That's good.
Maybe I'll have some put in.
Oh, my God.
Dumplings.
I wonder if it goes with the bean paste.
I'm sure.
Yes, it does.
There's chocolate in the dumplings.
I thought the bean paste was chocolate.
I think it's delicious with chocolate.
I like sweet things.
Sweet.
But it's strawberry chocolate.
That's all.
It's kind of... it's got a nice burnt look to it.
Oh!
What? It's got feathers!
It has wings!
It looks so good!
Of course it does.
Wow, that looks delicious.
Next time, it's cooked medium, right?
Yeah, I was told well-done.
Dumplings.
Go ahead, Hono-chan, eat some more.
Oh, you don't mind?
Then eat some more.
Eat some more.
Um...
Oh, I'm on a rampage.
I'll have a rampage dumpling.
It's my first time here.
Oh, yeah, right.
Yes, um...
I couldn't come on our first anniversary.
I'm sorry.
Just the needle tail.
I see.
I couldn't come.
I saw you there.
Oh, I see.
It's a bird's-eye view.
That's not the first episode.
That's sad.
I had to eat.
Do you want some tea?
Can I have some tea?
Sure.
Thank you very much.
Which is better, tea or green tea?
Wrong.
Choice.
the latter
The latter green tea
The one that's not green tea.
Okay then.
Marie, green tea.
And the sauce is oolong tea.The sauce is oolong tea.
Yes, it's oolong tea.
You have oolong tea?
I want oolong tea.
I prefer black oolong tea.
Oh, we don't have that.
Shall I get some?
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
They'll get it for me.
He'll get it for you.
I can do it. I'll be a junior.
I'll get you some more Taleuron tea.
Marie, this is Prue.
Really, you can eat it!
It's freshly baked!
Oh, yeah.
That's freshly baked!
It's so cute.
It smells so good.
As soon as you walk in...
As soon as I came in.
I could smell it.
I could smell it on you.
It's amazing.
You must have been hungry.
I don't eat.
Eat up.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Marie...
Yes, ma'am.
You were practicing earlier.
Yes, I was.
I was.
I was impressed.
He was a good kid.
Oh, my gosh.
Yay!
We did it!
We've been working so hard. We've been working so hard.
Thank you very much. We're doing great.
You're really going to sit in the chair.
I'm going home. The Chairman is going home too. I wish he'd go home.
Then we'll continue to sit in the chairs? We'll continue to sit in the chairs?
We'll sit in the chairs off-camera, too? Yeah, that's a good idea.
Just the dumplings. That's a good idea.
Pekka? Tissue pecker?
Tissue case that looks like a mouth. They're so cute! Nico!
Smile stick! I miss it!
You were drinking from the Happy Smile Tour, weren't you?
I made a fistful of tea. No, it's not a fistful.
I've been getting cold feet from Komisan since a while ago.
The moment I asked him to pom-pom me, he threw up all over me.
Isn't she a super sadist? Yes, I'm an S.
You're so sweet to me, Kumi-chan.
Do you have love for us? If so, can you love us?
Is there love there?
Dumplings filled with love! Yes!
Cute, you're so pushy. I'll leave you to it.
Nico's the only one who ate it. You can take it home with you.
Then why don't you take some and put some chocolate on it? It's our guest.
So it's newly wrapped.
Why don't you two try? I can't get it. It's a waste of batteries.
You want me to make it? I'll just have this well-done one.
Wow, that's great. First time well done.
That's great. You're gonna be so professional by the end.
Hold a couple of these. Wow, right here. You can see them.
Choco, you sounded like a meth head.
I like you, Kumi, so I did it alone.
I'm sure people who are watching noticed. I thought you weren't watching.
I'm sure there are people who are only awake.
A piece of chocolate? He wants to eat it, don't you?
Sure! Sure? Looks delicious.
But the yatsuhashi was raw. You want to eat it as it is?
No, it's fine.
Can I have it?
Have fun. Thank you for coming. I hope you all come again.
Thank you for bringing the silver shield.
A silver shield? Yeah, yeah, yeah!
He's gonna have so much fun.
I've been studying the angle of view for a while, and this is what I've come up with.
Flip-flop. - Flip-flop.
I'll see you soon.
Want to try some cheese?
Cheese sounds delicious!
Chocolate and cheese.
Thank you.
Right in front of you.
Look at the reflection in the silver shield.
Yes, it's a reflection.
Do you see it?
What do you see?
It's hard to tell through the screen.
Looks good.
What do you think, now?
Almost there, almost there.
Almost. I can see it, I can see it, I can see it.
Wait a minute. Is this mine?
Which way is this?
It looks a little more this way.Looks a little more this way.
Is the rotation this way? Or the other way.
This way. What do you think?
A little more?
How's it coming? Is it done?
A little?
It's a little bit.
I see something.
No, those are dumplings.
Those are dumplings.
This one?
But I think everyone can see them.
I'm sure.
If you took a screenshot of this miraculous moment, please don't miss it.
Don't miss it.
Don't blink.
You can eat the dumplings.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
I know.
It's a weird thing to do.
I was going to split it in two.
The chocolate that came with me.
Is that all you brought, Marie?
I brought the ornaments.
I see.
Ornaments.
It glows.
That's great, but it glows.
It's a little bright.
Thank you very much.
What do you like?
I don't wear it.
That's great.
That's really good.
Oh, hey.
Where's Marie?
Where do you sell it from?
Vinegar...
Vinegar? I like vinegar. Only vinegar?
Vinegar and what do you have?
Soy sauce, vinegar, and ponzu.
I would like to have some ponzu.
Konka's letter.
Konka, you really ate it.
Thank you very much.
Did you get my comment?
How's the air conditioning?
It's fine.
If you don't mind.
Yes, please.
Eiko's little girl.
Kon-chan, he says he's going to yoo-hoo.
I'll yuck it up.
Stop it. Stop. Stop.
Marie..,
What? She's writing.
Do you remember?
Three years.
I remember so much.
Bye-bye.
Oh, did you have a camera?
Please don't tell me.
I was about to run away.
Please stop him. Shideto.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Have fun. I'll be watching.
Oh, chopsticks. You can't eat without chopsticks.
Thank you very much.
Do you have chopsticks? Here.
These are mine.
Sure.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Wait a minute, there's another one over here.
Here it is.
Eat.
Bon appétit.
I'm so happy.
What is this?
Let's eat.
Bon appétit!
Looks so good, it's really good.
Bon appetit.
Bon appetit!
Scary.
Which way should I start?
Are you okay?
It's a hedgehog!
It's Harwich!
Are you okay?
Where are you? Where's Harwich?
It's about this way.It's about this way.
Are you okay?
Actually, I don't think it's no good.
I'm going to be the guy who does it to get the pearl.
It's a little hard for me to be on stage.
We've been practicing for the show. Just the two of us.
This is really,
It's a big win.
It's not good.
It's so beautiful,
You're going to eat it like this?
I usually make it in a frying pan,
But you can do it like this.
Bon appétit.
I'm so happy.
It's your first time.
I was listening to you and my mom,
While we were eating.
It's good.
Do you have handhelds?
Handhelds?
We don't have hand-held shots.
That's all we have.
I see.
But you said I could bring that.
It's Hollywood rust.
I ate it.
Do you want another one?
Sure.
You sure?
That's great.
I tend to do this when people are talking.
I wanted to eat Sumi's game.
Really?
I'm glad you did.
How was it?
It's good.
It's really good.
Delicious?
I want to hear it, Morimoto.
Umaporu!
So cute!
How is it?
What's that?
It's called "Umaporu".
It worked. Thank you very much.
I'll have some.
I'm sorry.
I'm on the other screen now.
Bon appétit. Looks delicious.
Thank you.
It's so lonely. I'm the only one here.
Bon appétit.
Thank you.
Not too hot? Mm-hm.
What do you think?
What do you think? What do you got?
What do you got? Because you asked for it.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Is it out already? Yeah, yeah.
What? What? It's not coming out?
Not yet. Not yet.
Is it because you swallowed it? That's right.
After I tasted it. Not yet?
Yeah, yeah.
Yum!
That's great.
I got the feeling.
What was that?
It was so distorted.
Wait, Kumi-chan.
Maybe it's not what you're looking at.
Like this side.
It beeped at my eyes.
Thank you.
Can I put it a little further back?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
A little further over here, on Marie's side.
Is that a good angle?
It's slanted.
Like this.
Definitely at an angle.
Is it?
It's done.
It's too delicious.
I love it.
It's time to need it tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
It was sudden, wasn't it?
Good for you.
If the rain forecast says so.
I'll be fine.It's all right.
We are always warm.
It's going to be fine.
It will be fine.
Even if it's raining, it's sunny.
As long as you are there.
It's wonderful.
I was moved.
I'm touched.
Yumi, you don't say anything like that anymore.
You don't say anything anymore.
Words from Osaka's camera.
Hey, smile.
It's been three years and I've grown so much.
Smile.
Sit down like this.
I was in there with everyone.
You were smiling.
Like Kemichan.
Like Keimi-chan.
Hey, what?
I think she's the type.
That's right.
She's not used to being told what to do.
It's funny.
Unlike the other two.
I haven't been told that either.
I'm not used to being told that either.
I haven't been told either.
That's amazing. Looks delicious.
It's baked.
Maybe it's pretty well-done.
Weldon.
What does "well done" mean?
It means "tanned.
I like tanned.
Really?
Because I get sunburned at a much higher rate.
Is it still hot?
Yes, it's hot.
But this one looks pretty good.
Which one?
This is the first one.
I think it's sharky.
This one has a lot of oil.
I'll wipe it off.
Hold on.
Does it ever fly like this?
Let's get out of the way a little bit.
I think I'm done.
I think I'm done. I can't see.
The part with the dumplings.
I heard there's about 30 seconds.
There's a lot of time. It's pretty good.
He's still working on the first pitch.
No way! That long?
I get nervous.
I get so nervous.
Don't lie! I'll be fine.
But the most important thing right now is whether the weather will be fine or not.
You went to see it, didn't you?
It rained a lot, but we did it.
It was really cold, wasn't it?
It was cold.
You went to see Harumi and me, right?
Around April.
That's right. We went to Tamaska.
It was raining really hard.
I really had to take an umbrella. I couldn't walk.
Seriously?
Buy one.
I wore a kappa, didn't I?
I look like this.
Harumi's kappa.
I bought one folded up like this.
I have one like this.
I have one too.
It was such a small bag.
I wondered where it was, but it was from OK.
It's amazing. It's super big.
It was tiny.
It was like this.
When I opened it, it was plastic.
It was just a garbage bag with a hood.
Was it usable? Really.
Really. But it looked like that.
It was like Oblate.
Oblate?
It's not oblate.
Grandpa is a Smurfs.
What is it?
I don't know.
I don't know what Oblate is.
You mean this?
The kind you put on when you shampoo?
After shampooing.
After shampoo.
What do you mean?
Oblate.
What's oblate?What is "obblate"?
You mean like "ostracism"?
Is that what it is? Who is it?
Have you ever heard of "Bonterme"?
Bondermé?
What's that?
Bontermé.
That's it, isn't it?
That's what I'm talking about, right?
I'm about number one this year.
It's not that interesting.
When we say we don't run.
It's like Haraji's comic dialogue.
Please stop it.
I want to say it again.
When you take medicine with grandpa with that.
Like the paper that melts when you take medicine with grandpa.
That's enough.
Look it up later.
I'll look it up later.
It's really interesting.
It's too funny.
Is she getting the message now?
I think it's coming through.
I don't know if I'm saying it right now.
We're talking about baseball here.
As long as it's clear by the time the ball is played. That's right.
That's right. If it rains a little.
Oh, I see. We extended it then, too, and it started at 6:30.
That's right. I see.
No problem. Thank you. I'm a sunny girl.
Sunny girl. Sunny girl.
Sunny girl. Eat a lot.
I eat a lot.
Did you eat, Chris? He's eating.
I'm looking forward to making it. I'm going to eat it fresh.
It's delicious.
I'm going to eat the one that's not verdant. I'm going to eat the verdant one.
It's already been 40 minutes. Surprise. I'm surprised.
Since the event started. Two people are coming.
I'm like, "Well, I'll look at my watch,
I said, "Well, I'll look at my watch, so I'll be fine,
I told the staff, but I couldn't see it at all.
I was like, "Oh, I don't know where it is. I'm so embarrassed.
It's in my hand.
It's bad, but I've been doing it for hours now.
But I definitely can't push it today.
I see. That's right.
I'll take it.
Oh, please, please.
Bon appétit.
Hot.
That's freshly baked Japan.
I can't bake chocolate for spring at all.
I'm baking it. I made a mistake.
I made a mistake. I touched it again.
Is it hot?
Are you okay?
Is it really good?
Yes, it's good.
It's hot.
It's very stylized.
Cat tongue? Pal?
Anything goes if you put palu on it.
Mnh-mnh.
I'm not good at drinking tea. With a cup.
I try to drink it in an area larger than my mouth, so it comes out of here.
Please stop. Have you been doing this for years?
I've been drinking from a cup for quite a long time.
What is it?
How long have you been drinking?
I had a glass when I was little.
You didn't drink when you were little.
This is it.
So, I have been drinking from this cup since I was about 2 years old.
So, I have been drinking cups for 27 years, about 25 years.
I am a senior.
I'm still a novice.
From now on?
From now on, right?
Can I put all the garbage on the floor?
You can't see it, so don't worry.
You can't see it, so it's fine.
It's good.
There's a trash can.
I didn't notice.
Did I put my mouth in there?
I can't get this out.
It doesn't work.
Winter box. Winter Box.
Are you okay?
Excuse me. I was just eating.
You're right.
You came at me, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, no. It's bad if I guessed.
It's bad, isn't it?It's bad, isn't it?
Again?
Again with the extreme testing.
There it is.
Thank you.
That's great.
I'd like to take a look.
It says black.
The dumplings are delicious. Very good.
They are really delicious. Gyoza.
I'm too happy. Really.
It's like coming to Kumi's house.
Indeed. You're here.
It's Kumi's house, right?
It's Kumi's house.
It's beautiful.
I have all the classes and gold shields to myself.
At Kumi's house.
Why do you display them in your house?
But it has to be displayed somewhere, right?
Then I thought it would be fine at my house.
I think it's nice.
It's nice.
When you say it like that, I can't say anything.
It's amazing.
I'd like to sit down.
You can sit down.
Shall we sit down?
Isn't it dangerous?
I'd like to sit on the sofa.
With a golden shield?
I'd like to sit on a golden shield.
Okay, I'll take it.
Great.
What kind of shield is this?
But it's pretty light.
It's lighter than I thought it would be.
Really. That's amazing.
I admire it.
It's really thanks to all of you.
Thank you very much.
I'm a little greasy.
Sorry. I splashed oil.
On your drink.
It's totally fine. I don't mind.
I don't mind.
I'm glad I'm a girl who doesn't mind that kind of thing.
Next time, I'll have the girl who doesn't mind sit in the middle.
That's right. That's true.
I'm glad that we could do things like this again, like the dumpling party with everyone.
I'm glad.
We should do it regularly.
I'd like to do it. How about once a month?
Monthly?
How about once a week?
Once a week?
I'm really good at takoyaki.
Oh, really? That's amazing.
Rolling.
Rolling?
That's amazing.
I don't know, I can't open it at all.
Suddenly, it's not making any sound at all.
It doesn't make this kind of noise.
What? What? Like a clam.
Oh, my God. Breathing.
It's opening up, now.
But...
It looks hot. It looks hot.
Oh! It looks good. Look at it.
You can't see it.
It's hot.
It's dangerous.
Thank you for bringing it here.
Is this one good too?
Oh, is that it?
I thought it might go with the seeds.
It goes well with seeds?
I thought it would go well with seeds.
Goes with seeds?
Yes, chocolate.
Not chocolate.
I want chocolate.
I've got some right here.
My half of the chocolate.
It's delicious.
It's my first time to eat this chocolate.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's delicious.
There's a random piece of cheese in it.
If you haven't eaten it at all, that means it wasn't good.
It's delicious.
Can I eat it? A lot.
I want you to eat a lot.
You'll run out.
Are you okay? There's still one more seed.
I'll put in a lot.
I've been planning to mass produce.
How many can you make?How many can you make?
Maybe you can make a hundred or so.
We have enough for everyone.
Come and have some.
LOL!
And the lips, too.
My lips are tied. All of them.
Kyoko does it sometimes.
I can see that.
Kyoko plays games all the time, right?
That's right.
You've been doing a lot of it lately, haven't you?
Lately. With the switch,
You know, you just pop it on the switch.
I'm playing the same game all the time.
I see.
I think it's time for me to start playing Zelda.
What? That makes me happy.
Let's do it.
I should have done it earlier.
I was busy.
I'm glad. I'll do it.
I was thinking of doing it today.
Let's do it.
I'll do it.
It's really delicious.
Really? Really?
I want to eat 100 of these.
I'm so happy.
Spring, I can't tell if there's cheese in it.
What? Is there a lot of cheese in it?
I only put one.
This one is good too, right?
May I? Eat it.
It's hot.
It looks like my plate.
No?
Yes.
Come on in.
Really?
It's been that long?
It's early.
It's 8:47.
Silent.
Smells good.
Delicious today, too.
Welcome.
Would you like some of this?
It's hot.
Would you like to eat it upstairs?
Oh, no, we have another visitor.
There were no cushions.
What was that?
He was sitting in a triangle.
Sitting in a triangle?
Welcome.
Sorry.
Who cares about splashing oil on your drink?
It's okay.
People who want to eat.
Can't you let me put it on a plate?
It's hot.
Be careful.
Maybe we won't be able to eat during the delivery.
What a surprise!
Hina-chan and Hiyo-chan are here.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you very much.
I can't believe I'm doing this now.
Did you see it?
I didn't.
That's unusual.
You've seen most of it.
I saw a little bit.
Of course you did.
I had to be quiet.
There's cheese in it.
Thank you.
A new one.
I don't miss it.
Hiyoko likes Triangulum, too.
I like it a lot.
But recently.
She said the gyoza boom has already passed.
I made a pointed remark.
Kamusu.
I love dumplings so much.
There's a time for that, right?
Is it Chinese cabbage today?
Chinese cabbage.
It's crispy.
I'd like to eat it freshly baked.
Please don't make it plain.
I don't want it to be plain.
The chocolate was delicious.
Was it good?
It was delicious.
The chocolate looks delicious.
Did it burn a little?
No, it's not.Different.
Meat roast.
First.
You're leaving?
I have to go home, right?
I'm going home.
Was it fun?
It was fun.
This was good.
For the first time in a year.
First time in a year.
It's really the first time I've been here.
First visit.
Is it a store?
Thank you.
If there's any left, please go there for a while.
I'll be back to eat again.
I'll make a lot of food, so please wait for me.
I'll eat them all.
Please stop.
They look delicious.
I'll take one and go home.
Take one and go home.
Want some tea?
What would you like?
Thank you very much.
Come again.
I'll be back.
Thank you very much.
Marie.
Marie, your voice was pretty high.
Today.
Maybe it was fun.
It was fun.
Plus one.
I did it. Thank you.
You want to take this home?
Sure, drinks.
Bon appétit.
Yay.
Thank you for the drinks.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the food.
You've got everything you need.
What's good?
Anything.
Tell me what you like.
There's everything, isn't there?
Anything.
How much can I say? This.
How much can I say?
What do you drink?
There is such a thing as a drink, isn't there?
Not a proper name, but a concept.
An apple.
There is no such thing.
There's everything.
But then, why not this?
I don't understand.
Apple juice.
Surely, if you think of apple juice, it's apple juice.
Thick apple juice.
That's for sure.
What would you like to drink, Mr. Eyu?
I'm going to have shuwashuwa.
Shuwashuwa.
Do you have it?
Maybe this.
A little Coke.
It's definitely a Coke.
Look at the sizzle.
It's true.
Thank you very much.
All right!
Ready, go!
Thank you for your hard work.
You can see the comments here.
Really.
Really?
He said, "Good luck with the schedule. You said that, didn't you?
It's gone.
He says it's hot.
Then I'll make a new one.
That's great. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
But you know, no matter how I tried, I couldn't get it to show up, so I decided it's okay since I've seen it once.
Be careful.
Oh, I'm so happy.
Hiyotan, are you going to eat gyoza?
I want to.
May I?Good?
Do you eat well?
I eat a lot.
Oh, really?
Yes, I do.
Well, that's a little embarrassing.
Really?
That's amazing. Are you sure it's handmade?
Yes, it is. All of it.
I made it from scratch.
I forgot to tell you about the special today. It has garlic.
It's great.
You like garlic?
I love garlic.
Buy the one called black garlic,
I've never had black garlic.
Black garlic. It's a little bit, you know, sour.
I put it in.
Have you ever had garlic look good on someone?
No, I don't think so.
But Hiyotan always says that garlic looks good on dumplings.
That's right.
What?
I'm always concerned about it.
It's not like that.
But, you know, garlic has nothing to do with dumplings, right? Not really.
Not really. Yes, it does. Quite a bit.
I am sensitive to the smell of garlic.
Then they think so.
That's dangerous.
Next time you think of me, do it like a "boi-pa".
Next time, do it like a boy band.
A little bit like a boyie-pah.
Next time.
Tell me next time.
Okay, I'll do it.
If you smell garlic,
Garlic.
You are a garlic girl.
It won't hurt if I say, "Sure, you're a garlic girl," right?
Yes, that's right.
Sorry. Garlic chan.
I saw it for the first time today. Me.
That's right.
I'm glad.
We're at 40,000.
It was 30,000 earlier.
Earlier was when it started.
That's amazing.
She's so cute.
I wrote "cute" on it.
No way!
Thank you.
But it's really fun. I don't know if I can handle it this loosely,
But it's fun. It's amazing.
We're bringing you our usual self.
That's for sure. It doesn't feel like we're doing much.
I don't know, I feel like I'm rolling my own camera.
That's for sure. I'm filming.
It's like he's playing at filming.
That's amazing. This is how you do it.
It's fun.
Wait, can you bake some more? I was wondering what you're putting on the small side.
Here Hupan brought it.
Ta-da!
What?
He's happy.
Why?
These are my favorite souvenirs from Fukuoka, and they are called Tsuru-no-ko and Membe.
I know menbe, but I've never heard of tsurunoko. I knew Tsuru-no-ko, but I had never heard of menbe.
That's why I like them so much these days.
But I've never had them. Me neither. Taste.
Oh, it tastes different.
I've had the normal one before.
It's a souvenir.
Souvenir?
Did you bring it as a souvenir or did you bring it to put in?
Either way, it's fine.
It's sweet.
Is it sweet?
I'm going to do 10.
I've been getting in trouble for not timing my 10's right.
What is it?
Kon-chan, Hario and Marin.
Sounds good.
The menju looks delicious.
I'm glad. I like menbei.
And it's mayonnaise flavor.
Can I have it?
Wait, Marii, you forgot this.
I'm sure you did.
Did I get a good look at this?
Gyoza.
They're cute.
I'm going to buy some next time.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
I think I'm going to eat it,
I'm going to eat it.I think I'll eat it, I'll eat it.
There's some kind of sea chicken or something. Eh.
That's a substitute for dumplings. I've never eaten that much.
I mean, I put so much cheese in it. It's totally delicious. Are you okay?
I love cheese.
If you want regular dumplings, they might be a little cold.
Wow, there's chocolate too.
Hariyo brought the chocolate.
Choco choco.
You can do combined dumplings, right? Without putting them inside.
What's a combination dumpling?
You just eat the dumplings and then eat the chocolate.
You mean you can combine them with your mouth?
With mouthfuls.
Ten mouthfuls?
Yes, 10 mouthfuls.
That's smart.
That's great. That's what I'm talking about.
Wow, I like it already.
That's great. It's made to look like a feather.
Yes, I like feathers. I'm a little fat.
I like them crispy.
The grill marks.
It's nice.
Good night.
Hamagishi Hiyori English Kawada de kun, it says.
So please know Rito.
Thank you very much.
Is everyone else eating too?
Certainly. Just until 9:00.
I want to eat dumplings with you.
Do you make gyoza? At home.
Like this.
At your uncle's house?
He used to make them.
That's right.
I don't think we had dumplings at home very often.
Even though they are very tasty?
It's fun to taste the different flavors when you eat them at a restaurant.
I think they are all different.
They are all different, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
It's good.
Sorry.
I'll take a good one.
Well, how about this?
I'm on the rails again.
Oh, wow!
Oh, it's good, it's good.
Beautiful.
It looks a little.
Eh, it looks so delicious.
Both ends lined up.
It's baked nice.
Here you go.
Bon appetit.
Thank you for the food.
You shouldn't eat that.
You want some?
Yes, I do.
Don't eat it.
Until then, thank you.
Okay. Why do you want some? What? Sure.
Ponzu, soy sauce, vinegar.
Rayu.
What do you usually eat it with?
Usually, I eat it with ponzu (Japanese citrus juice). But I also mix soy sauce and vinegar.
What did you do here?
I just dropped something, my body.
Sewing machine.
I'm scared.
Do you need one?
I think so.
Yes, I think so.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
What do you want?
I'll make ponzu. Ponzu.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
What did you eat it with?
I tend to eat a lot of ponzu.
Maybe I'll have some too.
I'll have ponzu too.
Ponzu?
Yes, I'll have ponzu.
Thank you.
Too much? Yeah. Not at all.
Can I eat this? Yes, I'm sure.
I'm looking forward to it.
Bon appétit.
Wow, it looks delicious.
It's my birthday today. What? Happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
No, it's okay.
Is this, uh, is this what you're talking about?
Oh, yeah, yeah. You want to try it?
Let's do it.Let's do it.
Oh, I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's smeared.
It's going to smear, isn't it?
Here we go.
It's a bit of a liability.
I'll be fine.
Are you sure?
He's cute.
I just saw it.
It's cute.
Here, eat.
Eat it.
Looks hot.
You don't mind if I watch?
You look hot.
Ha!
Is this close to a cuter?
Mmm.
Is it good?
I've never seen it before.
Oh, I'm so happy.
Well, I'll get it for you.
Thank you, Cuta.
I'm sorry.
Did you say something?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Is everything okay?
That'll do.
Hey, hey, can I see you for a second?
I'm a little lonely. These two are so cute.
Oh, I can be right again.
Tom and Jerry. Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.
Yum! Yum!
It's so good. It's so good. - It's good?
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Hot?
Just right. It's not hot.
It's not hot. I don't know why.
Was there cheese in it?
What? There's no hiyota in it.
Maybe they didn't put any.
It's so cute.
I'm so happy. I'm glad.
Do you want some too, Misa?
I'll do it.
I'll be in the middle.
I'll go.
Thank you.
Here?
Yes, it's good. It looks good.
This is good, right?
What? Are you kidding me?
I've never seen this before.
You mentioned it earlier, right, Hirotan?
I saw it.
I saw it for the first time.
Eat up.
I'll have another one.
You remember?
What's that? It's kind of crooked.
What do you think? I think it's skewed a lot.
Yes, it's a little bit, but it's definitely skewed.
Oh, really?
When you put it back on...
That's okay.
But it comes back.
It's not working.
I'll put it back on.
Thank you very much.
What do you think?
Maybe it's a little crooked.
A little sideways?
Like this?
What do you think? What do you think?
How's it look?
This way.
This way? Oh, it's like this, isn't it?
How's that?
It looks good.
Thank you. - Oh, really?
Oh, really? Can I do this for a second?
Okay, that's enough. It's okay, right?
I'm thrilled, thrilled, thrilled, thrilled.
So, are you guys with me, or do you want to wear this, Hiyutan?
Oh, it's so cute. Is it okay? You can wear it.
I wanted to wear it.
Really?Really?
It looks good on you.
It sure does. I'm wearing white today.
You're cute as a cloud.
What's that?
This is Fumi's precious thing.
If I wear it, I'll turn into a dumpling lady.
It's fun.
Are you going to eat it?
Can I?
You're bringing the dumplings?
I'm still baking.
There's more to come.
In fact, I thought people would eat more,
I'm preparing a lot of dumplings.
I want to eat all of them.
I want to finish it.
I don't want to eat it all.
How many peels are there? All of them.
All the peels?
There must be about 100 peels.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hm.
Maybe not the cheese ones.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, is that it? Did it run away?
Cheese, run!
Too fast.
Ha-ha-ha.
Hee-hee-hee.
Delicious.
Good, I'm glad you guys like it.
I want to use it up upstairs.
That's great.
You're good at this.
But you know, I've been doing this since I was little.
I've been told I'm slanted.
Maybe it's a slant.
You're right.
Yes, you're right.
How's it going?
Maybe I went a little too far.
Oh, that's about right.
It's good, right? Yeah, it's good.
Really?
Thanks.
Okay.
Hey, hey, do you know what an oblate is? Yeah, I know what it is.
You know what it is, right?
I didn't know those two guys.
The fifth one, right? That's right.
The one that looks like melting paper.
Those two guys didn't know what an Oblate was.
The music one?
Metronome.
Vibrato.
I've been doing that all day.
What?
It was fun.
Vibrato.
Metronome.
You're good at electro.
I love it.
I'm talking about the childhood stuff.
That was on the air, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
Ah!
Hello.
Oh, there it is!
Who's there?
Hello.
I brought a lot of stuff.
He's a voice actor.
He's a fashionable guy.
Welcome.
Should I take down one of the cushions?
I did that. Sorry.
Excuse me.
Come in.
Hello.
I'm glad you're here.
I'm a little nervous.
I brought a lot.
Sorry. So many.
Wow.
There are so many souvenirs.
I chose the ones that I thought would be delicious if I put them in.
Thank you so much.
I'm so glad.
Can I put it in?
Can you put them in?
So many.
Thank you so much.
I was really looking forward to it.I was really looking forward to it.
Really?
Even when we were waiting.
Did you watch?
I did.
They're cute.
Three of our fourth graders are here.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
You're the fourth term students, right?
Yes, I am.
Nice to meet you.
I am Hirooka. Pleased to meet you.
I am Mizuki Hirooka.
I am Kuchijima Perfume. Please take care of me.
I am Garin Garin.
I am Haruka Yamashita. Please.
Haruka Yamashita.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Wait a minute. I'll bake it right away.
Thank you.
You want some of that?
Did you come here to put it in? Or were you going to grill it?
I've chosen something that I think will be delicious.
Why? Why are they so good?
What?
You want some?
You don't want some?
You can have some.
You can have these two right here.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
I'm glad you're here. I was doing something, so everyone was here. Except for Haruyasu.
For the first anniversary, you know, for the 4th year.
I wanted to do it for the 4th year, too.
Thank you very much. I'm glad.
I'm glad. I'm glad you came.
It has black garlic in it, right?
Is it? How did you know?
I've never seen it.
Or the picture.
You haven't?
It's just a little bit. Did you feel it? Black, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
I've never held it before.
It's surprisingly light. You're wearing it like crazy.
It's heavy.
100,000.
Are you okay?
It's cute.
Are you a member of the Black Garlic Independence Party? Definitely not.
It's like this display without a pause. I'm not... It depends on where you are.
Maybe it depends on the place.
You are very good at it. Yes, you are. I'm a dumpling girl.
I'm glad. I'm glad you all came. Do you like gyoza? I love dumplings.
When I came here today, I was clamoring for Chinese food. I made a fuss about it.
I heard that you eat dumplings. What do you mean, you eat dumplings?
That's right.
I'm glad. Don't forget.
Gyoza is Chinese, too. Of course they are.
What's Chinese? What do you do with them?
Put them in? What do you do with it? Should I change it?
You can go ahead. Go ahead.
Is it good? Go ahead.
Here, have some of these. Bananas.
Dessert. I want a banana.
We have bananas, too.
Yes, we do. We have chocolate, you know, chocolate and bananas.
We have bananas.
Then, I'll bake it normally first. Okay.
I'll take care of it. Thank you very much.
Once. Is it good?
Chocolate banana is good, and chocolate marshmallow is good too. Sure thing.
You put them in instead of dumplings.
I also like the combination of sausage and cheese.
It's amazing. Hokkaido people are good at that.
What's that? It was here first.
The rice is delicious. It sure is.
It's delicious.
Nagoya is delicious, too. It's delicious.
It's very rich. Yes, it is.
I love tabasaki.
It's delicious.
Megane cookies.
You gave me eyeglass cookies, right?
They were delicious. Really?
I'm glad.
We went to Fukui, didn't we? Really?
You did, didn't you?
He said he wanted to go to Micchan's parents' house.
That's right.
I want to go to my parents' house.
I'll invite you.
I'll watch your mother.
What? Really?
Micchan, Mom. She's happy to see you.
Is she lying?
I'm glad.Good.
Everyone, though.
I'm living away from my parents.
If you need anything, I'll read it. Anytime.
Thank you.
The forms are too awesome.
There are three of us, so it's full.
I think I'll make two rows.
Thank you very much.
The store is amazing.
It smells so good.
It's amazing.
The smell.
I was really attracted by the smell,
I was with Harusho's family just now,
It was the smell of dumplings,
I'm hungry.
I was a little bit,
I'm..,
Are you okay?
I just skated on my thumbnail.
It's my first time.
Just a second,
Hold on a second.
I'm just gonna skate on this.
You'll be here forever, right?
Someday.
Well, Kumi-chan, go home.
Sure, after you get back and relax.
Take it easy.
Take your time.
How long were we here earlier? Everyone.
They all came back soon.
Right.
Wow.
You didn't see them?
Oh, there he is.
Oh, I got it.
I got so many bug bites the other day.
About 10 bites.
What if it happens?
In the meadow?
In the meadow,
I mean, it's really a scald.
It's called a burn.
I don't have a cold, I have a burn.
My feet are all dried up now.
A little more.
Are you sure you put something on?
Yes, I am.
I'm applying it.
About five times a day.
The one you chose.
Yes, I did.
Let's do a scrub time.
Choose a piece.
Choose one piece.
That's it.
What do you got?
Did you do that?
I don't do seritori.
I have a special seritor for you,
Oh, Kumi-San. Kumi-san.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Kumi-san.
Oh, no, no, no.
I think Hiyotan is an idiot again.
What?
Let's do it with Kumi-san and everyone else, shall we?
Everyone doesn't know about Infinite Seritori,
I know this place.
It's called Mugen seritori,
It's our specialty.
I didn't know that. I didn't know.
We have a special skill.
Yes, it is.
It's great, really.
Really?
I was surprised.
He can do it at high speed.
Not many people can do that.
Okay, you want to go first?
Yeah, you guys suck.
Let's go!
Rascals, rascals, rascals, rascals, rascals, rascals, rascals, rascals, rascals.
Rumble, rattle, rattle, rattle.
Oh, my God.
We have to help.
It wasn't here.
Then leave this.
Okay.
Buy it.
It's floating. Cotocore air.
Sorry, sorry. Sorry.
With vapor.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thanks for the souvenirs.
Bye.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Suddenly very dry.
It's shopping.
I was already surprised. Just now.
That was amazing.
He said that to me all of a sudden.
I was listening to it.
I was reporting to the manager that I had found it.
I was listening next to him.
I was listening and wondering what was going on.
I heard "kokora kokora kokora.
They were doing it.
Yes.
Only those two could do that.
That's right. I don't think I can imitate them.
They really are Tom and Jerry.
That's what I think.
You must have gotten a lot of comments.
That's great.
Maybe he's still an otter koala. Maybe.
Otter Koala Zone.
It's still bad.
Wave to them.
I wanted you to wave.
I wanted to wave as much as I could.
I don't know, maybe I've never been in this situation before.
That's right.
I was alone and surrounded by 4th graders. I'm not surrounded.
I'm surrounded.
Surrounded?
It's difficult.
I was supposed to be surrounded.
Is that so?
Someone should ask you to sit next to him.
If we surround them, we can be next to both of them.
That's right.
If we go to the back.
We're surrounded.
Can I surround them?
Can we surround them?
I'd love to.
I want to be surrounded.
Let's do it.
How do you want to do it?
I'll sit in the middle.
Is that okay? Like this.
I'm glad.
I got it.
Here it is.
Can I sit down?
I opened this today.
I showed it off.
There's probably more women in there than in here.
Can I sit here?
Yes, you can.
I'm glad.
You want to go this way?
I'll go this way.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I'm so glad you let me surround you.
It's cute.
Nice. Senior.
Kaorin is surprisingly tall, isn't she?
I'm unexpectedly tall.
That's right.
I'm taller than Micchan.
Is that so?
Micchan is surprisingly small.
Mi-chan is taller than me, but she has a face,
I've been told I'm cute.
I think she's cute,
And Kaorin?
Oh, really? I didn't think so.
Surprisingly.
And Haruka?
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
Just like that.
We are about the same.
Now it's negotiation.
At 160.
I was 159.5.
Oh, really?
I thought you were 160.
Are you with me?
Then, yes.
Who?
In the morning.
Gravity does the work.
You can put your feet down.
Thank you very much.
Wow! Yum!
Wow! Feathers! Oh, my gosh!
Feathers. Oh, my God! It's true!
Excuse me if I have a moment. Yes.
I put it in the store.
It's very stable, without being careful. Thank you very much.
By the person sitting here.By the person sitting here.
Great feather in the cap for Micchan.
It works. Eh, excuse me.
It's got a great feather. That's great.
Let me give it to you. Oh, hey, thanks.
I'm getting a little Werdum, again. Werdum.
I'm getting Werdum because I'm having fun talking to you guys.
What's this? Looks delicious.
These? Dumplings.
What?
This? Please introduce them to us.
What is this? Gyoza.
Huh? Gyoza.
I bought dumplings.
You guys are so cute, you should take a picture. They're dumplings.
It's dumplings. I feel like, "Gyoza, gyoza, gyoza. Gyoza day trip.
It's done! Thank you very much.
Wait.
This is probably Hiyotan and Hina-chan, right? That's right.
Put this away once.
Put it away.
Okay, I'll put it here.
Sorry, I can do it.
I forgot to give out drinks and stuff to everyone.
There are some.
You do have it.
A big cup.
Yes, a big cup.
I saw it.
Yes, I watched it.
What was the most interesting scene?
When Kumi-San's dumplings were still on her head, and she opened this door, and the vapor burst out.
It was very interesting.
It's gushing out.
Kumi-san was releasing steam.
Sorry.
Is it okay to sit in the middle all the time like this?
Yes, thank you.
I forgot I was wearing it,
I forgot I was wearing it.
It was so funny. When I opened it.
What are you going to eat?
What should I eat with?
Chopsticks.
A matter of utensils.
I'm sorry.
I'll eat with chopsticks.
Instant.
Thank you.
Striking out.
I always eat it with ponzu.
How is it?
Yes, I do.
But we also have soy sauce and vinegar, and raayu.
I prefer soy sauce.
Soy sauce?
Yes, soy sauce.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Just soy sauce?
Soy sauce.
What's good?
Soy sauce mixed with vinegar?
I'll use soy sauce with vinegar.
Soy sauce with vinegar?
I'll have vinegar and soy sauce, too.
Soy-sauce with vinegar?
Sure, vinegar and soy sauce.
What's the ratio, about 1 to 1?
One to one? - Yes, about one to one. I'll leave it to you.
I'll make it two to one.
Which two?
Male 1.
Male one?
Yes.
I guess that's it.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
How about you, Porco?
I'll have ponzu.
It's my first time eating ponzu.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. You're a little far away now that you're sitting on top of me.
Are you okay?
You're out of the group, so please ask her to go downstairs.
I'll be next to you.
Thank you very much.
Yay!
Then, eat. Please eat.
Wow. Bon appétit.
I'm so glad, it's the first time I've had a fourth-year student eat it.
I'm so happy.
What should I do? What should I do?
It's pretty good.
Can you take it?
I'm happy.
I'm happy. Thank you.
Okay, I'm going to leave now.Well, excuse me for a moment.
Go ahead.
It's so big!
Oh, it jumped!
It's amazing! It's full! Are they all right?
There are so many of them. It looks like it can fly.
It looks like it can fly. They are flapping their wings.
Bon appétit.
It's really beautiful. It's amazing.
I'm nervous.
Let's take a picture of Micchan eating.
Oh, that's right.
I'll take a picture.
Thank you. Are you okay?
I'll go this way then.
Thank you very much.
I pushed something... again.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'll take the picture.
Thank you very much.
It's so cute.
It's so delicious.
Delicious?
Black garlic.
Are you listening?
I feel it.
You feel it?
It's delicious. I'm happy.
Good.
Then, a little bit for both of you.
Bon appétit.
Black garlic.
Is it good? Maybe it's a little hardened.
It's really good. Good?
Good. It's got a lot of juice.
It's good. It's good with the ponzu.
Match? You guys are the best. Food report.
The best we've had so far.
It's lovely. I'm so glad you guys enjoyed it.
Thank you.
You know, when you put them on the table, they tend to be on an angle.
I think it should be a little bit more towards the spring.
That's good. That's good.
Thank you very much.
I said a little more diagonal.
Right?
Do you want to try this?
You want to try it?
I'll do it.
I'm so happy. Eating dumplings with everyone like this. I'm so happy.
I've really wanted to eat them. Really?
You know, you guys are like that, right?
You know, living on your own...
Do you cook?
No, I don't.
Sometimes. Do you cook occasionally?
Sometimes. I've recently become addicted to it.
Oh, really? What do you think?
What do you make? I don't know, salad bowls or something.
What? What do you mean?
What? Oh, my God.
How fashionable.
I tear lettuce and put sweet potatoes on top.
Wow, it's delicious.
It's delicious.
It's delicious. Tearing lettuce.
Looks delicious.
I put some softened sweet potatoes on top.
Oh, you do that yourself?
That's right. That's right.
That's amazing.
Now you can make some kind of meat.
Pork? I also like pork shabu-shabu.
I like pork shabu-shabu.
That's amazing. Sorry.
I like rice.
Oh, you mean good rice. Well, I'm happy when I'm eating good food.
I am happy, really. I love rice.
If I could make it with my own hands, I would be very happy.
But only a little.
It's amazing.
You are becoming a good cook.
Can I make this too?
Let's make it.
Let me cook for you.
Cool.
I said it so loudly and so fast.
My favorite state.
I put banana and chocolate.
This is a sesame banana.
It's absolutely delicious.
It has sesame oil.
Don't worry.
It's delicious.
You can use any kind of sesame oil.
What would you like to put in it?
I don't know.
Marshmallows.
I want marshmallows.I want to eat marshmallows.
But I'm not sure if it's the skin.
Do you want to try putting them in?
Oh, no.
They'll melt if we leave them like that. They should be sticky.
That's true.
It might affect it.
If you roll up the skin, will it be sticky?
The inside will be sticky.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Do you want to try it?
Let's give it a try.
Do you want to wrap it up?
No, I don't know. It's a little bit like shumai.
I just got it out of the fridge.
What do you mean?
Wow, it really looks like shaomai.
Yes, it really is.
It's cute.
A flower.
Wow, stars.
Stars.
I want sausage and cheese.
Wow, looks delicious!
I love it!
Wow, do you think it'll cool down?
I'm Mitaka.
Mitaka.
I'm curious.
May I?
Sure.
Can I put this in? Can I put that in, too?
I want to.
I'll do it.
Thank you very much.
Okay, then, sweets.
Okay.
On the back.
Yes.
Some kind of cheese. What?
It looks like a piece of cheese. I didn't do anything.
You want to try one of these? Yeah.
Mochi, oh, I think I can fit two. Oh, wow.
I wonder what happens to rice cakes when they are baked. Wow, it looks delicious.
Won't it become soft?
But rice cakes are baked, aren't they? That's true.
I mean, it's probably already baked. I see.
The black part.
Looks delicious. Looks delicious.
This is my first time in this corner. Dumpling party history.
This is amazing.
What's that? The first one's in.
Ah! Here comes Ogoshu.
Here comes the hostess. Quiet. Thank you for your hard work.
I don't know if you guys can see me. Good work.
Wow, they look like a pair. You look like a pair.
Amazing. Footsteps.
We were just doing a fun corner. I was sandwiched in between.
Let me show you.
It's so cute.
We want you to show us.
Like this. It's not tanned.
I think it's undercooked.
I'm baking it right now.
And the same color.
The baked one.
Oh, really?
I don't think anyone's figured that out yet.
It's one size bigger than that.
What are you talking about?
The pot.
I'm Kaho. I'm not a friend.
I'm in elementary school.
I'm a high school student.
But still young.
I see it a little in front of me.
I'll put it down for once.
I'm not sitting here.
I'm not sitting.
You are sitting down a little.
First of all, you should get involved.
I was like, "An.
Really?
I didn't know what to do with it.
Looks delicious!
It looks delicious. The marshmallows are amazing.
They're melting.
It's a container.
The skin is definitely raw.
You're supposed to eat the skin.
I'm not supposed to eat it.
Three years ago.
Can I eat this?
Yes, you can.
Marshmallows.
I like marshmallows.
I love marshmallows.fondness
Oh, my God.
Not too hot?
Yeah, it's good.
Not too hot? I want to eat it so bad.
In a bowl.
Is it still raw? Is it too hard?
I don't like it raw.
But it's been cooked, so I don't know if it'll work.
Oh, my God.
Want to try it?
Oh, my God!
Looks so good!
Let's leave it.
How about some santarashi?
I think it looks tender.
How do you like it?
Chocolate banana!
Who's that?
Choco Banana!
Who's there?
Thud! Thud!
Toshiki!
You're early.
Looks delicious!
Has it started?
Only 30 minutes to go!
You're early!
Manners notice?
Are you sure?
Let's put it on top.
I thought I'd eat it for you.
I'll eat it.
May I have another one?
Can I have it?
Of course.
I'll have one.
Great.
Come on.
It's early.
Here we go.
I can't read your comment.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
It's good.
That's good.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
I'm glad.
Hey, I think we can go to Mitaka.
Yeah.
Want to try some?
I am.
Is it good?
It's good.
I don't know if I should eat this, do that, or take a turn.
I don't know.
Is this the one that Micchan made for me?
This is it.
Do you think it'll work?
I hope the cheese melts.
I want it to melt.
I want the cheese to melt.
I want the cheese to melt, don't you?
Yes, I'll give Haruharu a chocolate banana.
Yes! Thank you!
I ate it yesterday.
Really? Really?
Two days in a row.
That's great.
I'll give you this.
Thank you very much.
So, you don't have a bowl?
Here.
Yes.
I'll leave it here for once.
Thank you very much.
I'll finish it when I see it.
I haven't seen it.
No Micchan.
Lately, I can already eat the dumplings that Kumi made here, and I'm...
Cute.
It's a sense of enjoyment I'm glad I was born with.
Mi-chan is cute.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I'll try it then.
By all means.
The one you made.
It's fun. Here you go.
It might be hot.
I heard he saw it.
Here you go. I'm curious.
I'll take it.
Report back.
What do you think? Is it good?
Is it good?
It's crispy.
It looks soft. It looks delicious.
Yummy!Delicious!
Cute!
I'm reaching for it!
I can't wait to try it!
Soft and crispy rice cake.
Nice food report.
It goes so well together.
I think you should make more and more.
You should make more and more.
You should make it more and more.
This is delicious.
Yes, I'll try it.
Thank you very much.
It's chocolate banana. It's chocolate banana.
This is chocolate banana.
It's hot, for sure. Are you okay? You went in one bite.
Is it hot? I made you some tea.
Can I get you some? Gel?
Are you okay? It's delicious!
It's really starting to hit me now. Is it good?
It's good. Eat slowly. I'll be fine.
Are you sure?
Really?
Bananas are sweet.
Heat makes them sweeter, right? That's true.
Neck wild food. I interrupted you.
Is it good? It's a crepe.
Crepes? It's a crepe.
What's that? Mickey made sausage and cheese.
Wow! It's absolutely delicious.
It's delicious. It's filled with love.
Oh, here it comes.
Mmm.
It's delicious.
Wow!
It tastes like love.
I knew it.
Thank you guys.
Thank you so much.
I want you guys to...
I want you to eat that lovely baked good.
It's delicious.
It's amazing.
Suddenly, it eats.
Bing bong.
Bing bong and...
Toshiko-san came.
Delicious.
It is water for use.
I can't make it anyway, even if we eat with these two.
I'm too picky. I want to eat properly.
Me too.
I've got a baked one here, by the way, but it's probably a little cold.
May I? Before.
Good.
We're good.
It cooks this fast?
Yes, it is.
Very fast.
If you eat it with salt, it's already a rice cracker.
Rice crackers? Yes, like rice crackers.
Do you have salt? Salt, they might have it over there.
Isn't soy sauce good? Yes, I think so.
Can I bake them some more?
Miki, have some marshmallows.
Marshmallows?
Can I bake some more?
Can I hold this?
I got it.
Yes, ma'am.
Looks good.
Wow. You really do throw a party.
You just noticed? It's really a party, Micchan. It's a party today.
Party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party, party.
Look at this. Mee-pan, thank you. Mee-pan made these crackers.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Welcome.
The rice crackers with raayu sound delicious.
Oh!
Welcome!
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you very much.
Please, take a look around the store.
I'm wearing it right now.
You've heard of it.
Who has rice crackers? Eat.
Bon appétit.
It really is a rice cracker shop.
Don't you guys want a plate?
We don't have plates.
I have some right here.
I've got it.
I can't read that fast.
Hi, Grandma.
Aloha.
Aloha blows everything out of the water.Aloha blows everything out of the water.
What are these?
Cold dumplings.
May I eat them?
Eat it.
Gyoza.
Eat.
What might you make of this?
Shapes.
Sand?
It's cold.
Who wants crackers?
Rice crackers, yes, yes. I want some.
Here you go.
Yes, I'm eating it.
Those who have rice crackers, everyone.
Try some rice crackers.
You don't mind? Thank you.
It's so new.
It's hot.
It's good. I'll eat it with my hands.
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
I'll give it one more heat.
Bon appétit.
Shu-chan eats normally, right? Gyoza.
Shin-chan, gyoza.
I want some, too.
They're freshly baked.
Really?
Yes, they are.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Good.
I just baked it.
Yoshichan, let's eat gyoza together.
Eat.
Freshly baked?
I'll eat when I go downstairs.
I'd like to have some, please.
Please, come in.
Come in, both of you.
Maybe it's time.
Yes, it is.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
Certainly.
Say, "General Public Service CV".
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
Please spend some time.
Thank you. I saw many souvenirs.
They were delicious.
Please make this again.
Thank you very much.
Take care.
Let's eat again.
Mipan, come here.
Aren't you coming? Toshi-chan.
Hello.
Hello again.
I'm Shiho Kato.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
Tell me if you're going to wear light blue.
Poor you.
Poor Shiho.
Why did you say it was raining?
It's just like pom-pom, isn't it? As I recall.
Pom-pom-ko.
Without the ula-ula-ula.
Ullaura what to say.
Ippon
Oni miss
That's a zero sequence.
I'm going to eat this by myself again, aren't I?
I want to eat minpan. I'll bake it now.
Can I take this back one more time?
They say it looks like something.
Really? Yes, I'm sure. Thank you.
But you know what? I have an announcement.
That's right. I'm Katoh, who's playing with his phone.
I've been reading your comments.
Thank you so much. I couldn't read them all because they were so fast.
I was so nervous.
I got nervous.
You were nervous?
Can I cook now? Dumplings.
Thank you. Kumi.
I came here to eat. Really.
You guys are really nice to talk to me.
Let's talk.
I ate a few pieces and left.I ate a couple of pieces and left.
But I prepared a lot.
I'm going to eat it all and go home.
But I'm glad that everyone came in place of me like this.
I'm happy too.
Shiho-chan, you called me a gal.
I'm not a gal.
You're cute.
When I say I'm friendly with them, I get nervous.
I wondered if it's okay to drink anything on Youtube.
Like ponzu (Japanese citrus juice).
Do you have ponzu?
This?
I love the sun.
Ohitsu-sama.
It's delicious.
Did you say "happy alcohol" already?
Oh, no. I thought I slipped up.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Don't be silly.
It's okay.
It's good.
Can I oil it?
Ikki-San says it's time.
Is it?
It's Ikkii-san's time.
Last one.
Did I say last?
It's late at night.
I'll do it after Ikkii-san.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm sitting on the frame.
It hurts.
Now it's like this.
You're sitting on my leg.
See, these are my feet.
Isn't this amazing?
Silver shield.
Dumplings!
Are they real?
It says "Sunshine Dumpling Channel" on it.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad you're wearing fashionable clothes.
Who's that?
I used my handheld camera.
Mannequin Challenge
Yuna.
Hey, hey, hey.
Today.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, stop it!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
I can't do it.
Hey...
Hey, Mr. Minpan, you're making a fool of yourself.
Come on...
Come on, come on!
Ouch.
That was popular a while ago.
I think it's time for a reminder.
Wait, it's not too late.
But I can't push it today.
I know, I know, I know. I know why you can't.
Can I eat? Shi-Shi, which one can I eat?
Can I eat all of them?
I'm making fresh baked goods.
Do you have any soy sauce?
Is this the shishi's? Thank you.
I like ponzu.
Ponzu?
Oh, my God.
I'm glad I believed you.
Let's get Minpan and Kumi-chan.
Sasaki-kumi
Sasakimine
I'm Sasaki and Shiho
Everyone is a Sasaki
Delicious!
Bon appétit!
Kumi's homemade
I ate some of Minpan's homemade food
Maybe it's hot!
Very catty!
I love you, Tatoshi-chan!
I love you, too!
Thank you, Uncle!
I can only tell you through live delivery.
Thank you for everything, Uncle!
Thank you for everything.
Thank you for everything since the time of Kiraki Kiraki.
Eat 120 pieces, Toshi-chan.
That's the plan today?
I can't leave until I eat 120.
I can't go home.
But I'll finish the delivery.
Delicious!
Private.Private
Hey, you know, this is my first time playing this game.
I think it might be someone else, because I've been playing a game called "make it awkward" lately, and this time...
It's nice to meet you, but it's awkwardly awkward this time.
Good night.
This is not going to work.
Really?
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
The meat is firm. It's more firm than usual.
Because I ordered it.
I put black garlic in it today.
Oh, really?
Yes, I did.
I'm glad.
Just reheat it.
ASMR.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's about time.
Hey, Money is early. I've only been here about a minute.
Hey, please. After you've done all this, you can go ahead and eat.
Okay.
I do. But I wanted to let you all know today. All along.
It's not too late.
Ten minutes ago?
Maybe we can make it in 3 minutes. I'll be the timekeeper.
Okay, I'll play timekeeper.
But then we'll have to finish talking about it.
What do you mean?
Oh, I see. Then let's do it right now. Quickly.
Right now?
Okay, sunshine.
I've got a bit of a time leap here.
Time leap?
What's that called?
Revenger.
I have a big announcement today.
Time lag.
Not multiverse.
I have, uh, a big announcement today. To everyone.
The clothes in general are cute.
Very cute. Thank you.
Thank you.
Where's the trash?
Oh, no.
Old trains run on old rails.
There's a period announcement. It's really important.
No, it's not. Old trains.
No, it's not. A little more.
Hiragana-ko's. Old train.
I only know it from Hiraganako's song.
Indeed.
Cherine cries you like you do. Please listen.
Well, I'll be going.
Today, I have a big announcement.
There is.
I'll get it out.
It's pretty big.
It's really serious.
I'm nervous.
Here we go.
Ready?
There you go.
Big announcement.
Thank you.
Who wrote that?
Hina-chan did it for me.
She's cute. Hina-chan.
Some of you are still nervous.
I have a really important announcement to make today.
Hina-chan wrote this.
I did it on the left.
It's because we have a big announcement to make.
Is that what this is about?
Here we go.
Ready?
There you go.
We'll be releasing our 10th single on July 26th.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
You've been waiting for it, right?
That's great. But it's pretty early.
Yes, it's early. This time.
I think that's why I was surprised.
Let's go well.
Let's go.
Actually, we are in the middle of a production.
Dancing.
Dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing.
I have one more announcement to make,
Is the sound okay?
I'm at the Euler Center.
Hold on. Do you want me to hold it?
Just in time?
I'll cut my face.
The formation will be announced on June 18th at Hinatazaka.
That's why.
It's the 18th.
The formation will be announced this Sunday at Hyuga.
Uncle's.Uncle's.
Comments have stopped, haven't they?
They've stopped. You've been commenting a lot.
Thank you.
I don't know what to do.
I might have surprised you.
I was surprised, wasn't I?
It was really sudden.
Why did you stop commenting?
I'm most eager to see them now.
Has this ever happened to you before? Until now.
I've been streaming it.
Do you want to delete it?
Will the streaming end?
Do I have to reopen YouTube?
I wonder..,
I don't know.
Maybe you're starting to think so, too.
I wonder if it's the members who came today,
I'm thinking that Toshi-chan is here right now, so.... I wonder,
You have a very rich imagination,
I introduced him to a lot of people who came.
There it is!
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm glad you're looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it too.
No, no, no, it's early. It's not over.
It's early, isn't it? This time.
This year, we're going to be vigorous,
Yes, let's go. Let's go.
That's right.
I'll keep going and going.
You all should, too.
But I want to do a live concert in the summer.
I don't know anything.
I really don't know anything.
Yes, I don't know. It's a big announcement.
I'm really surprised at the big announcement.
I don't know anything about it.
Center dumplings.
Center dumplings?
Yeah. They're cute.
I can definitely eat this now.
Bon appétit.
I'm warming it up.
Aaaaah!
It's okay. It's not sauce.
Kyoko. Kyoko. Kyoko.
Kyoko and Amon Market.
We want to do live.
We want to do it live, don't we?
We want to do live. We want to do live concerts in summer.
WKBS is not going to be held this year, right?
Yeah, I know.
You discharged water, didn't you?
Yes, they did. I want to go.
Oh, it's delicious.
It's hot.
You forgot to drink your coffee.
Want me to turn it down a little?
Yes, that's right.
We'll be announcing more about this single in the future via live streaming,
I'll let you know when we do it, and we'll be doing another live stream on YouTube, so please watch.
I hope you all enjoy it.
Please watch it.
This channel is great.
It's great. It's very active.
I hope you guys enjoy it. I'm glad.
Follow and Good button.
Subscribe to our channel.
Please subscribe.
Lots of seeds. I'll eat them too.
It's delicious. Let's eat again, Kumi. Thanks for a good day.
Thanks for a day's work.
Thanks for the gyoza shop.
Today, today's business was also good.
A lot of cute girls came.
It was good.
Mmmm entonces.
Oh, but, you know, it's burnt, but it's good.
It's really good.
Tasty? I'm glad.
Freshly made is the best. I knew it.
Freshly made is the best.
The banana got burned.
It looks hot.
We'll relax at the end.
Yes, we are relaxing at the end.
Because it's a dumpling party.
It's fun, isn't it?
He asked for some hoi-mi. Hoimi.
Hoimi?
Yeah, I'll have a banana.
I'm sorry, I'm holding a banana.
Good luck with your work tomorrow.
Hoimi.
Now everyone is back.
Good luck with your work.
Rehoma.
That's great.
Even better.The more amazing ones.
Recovery.
Rehoma.
Yeah, it's good. Delicious.
I dreamed of performing at the Nissan Steamboat Stadium.
I want to do it. A stadium.
Nissan.
The National Stadium is our dream. We are.
I can't say much about it, but...
Please, sunshine.
Now meepan!
Thank you, Pinky.
Thanks a lot.
July 26th, right?
Yeah.
It's coming up.
July 26th?
That's fast! Almost there!
Surprise!
Here it is.
Don't you have to announce Shio-chan?
Ah! It's Shio! I saw it today!
Shio-chan's photo book.
Shio's ship-out photo book.
She was so cute. All of them.
They were really cute.
They were really stylish.
All of them are enjoyable.
The hashtag, Eye Tiger, will be released on June 20. Aloha!
Name Aloha.
Go shoot the whole film in Hawaii,
Fashionable, and the happy feeling of Hawaii is amazing.
The background was also very stylish.
It was really cute.
Of course, I think girls will be happy with it,
I think the girls will be happy, of course, but I think the male customers will also be happy,
It's a little embarrassing, isn't it?
Of course, we also have such photos,
It was really nice. It was really nice.
I'm getting a little embarrassed.
I'm glad.
You look great. Have confidence.
So please do me a favor.
Please help us get the social networking sites up and running.
Please lend me your help.
I'm looking forward to seeing you on social networking sites.
Hashtag EyeTai!
Let's get excited, everyone.
We want to meet Katsushika. Let's meet.
There's a Real Migli, isn't there, July?
Sure there is.
For the first time.
The first Real Migli in Corona Fall.
I'll see you in July.
Migli, online Migli...
Yes, there is.
I've been to Migli before.
It was fun. Today, too.
Is it over? It was short.
Five more minutes.
I think it's time to call it a day. Soon.
It's okay.
Two more minutes.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot.
You know, before we came here, we were both wearing lip balm with capsaicin in it.
We were both wearing lip balm.
We both have lacrimal lips,
I've really applied it before,
I think it's hot.
I think it's hot, it's hot and it tingles.
I hope everyone had a good time today.
It was fun.
Yes, it was.
It's almost over.
Two hours flew by in the blink of an eye. Indeed.
Two hours flew by. That's for sure. I wasn't on for two hours.
I don't know what's so interesting about Toshi-chan.
Was it the publicity? I wonder if the advertisement was funny.
I want to eat dumplings. If you think I'm funny, you've never met my kind of woman.
No? But no two people are alike.
That's for sure.
I heard you had a good time. It was good.
It's a little closer to the end, actually, that's for sure. Just a little bit.
That's right, that's right.
Age blood. Year-old blood.
Oh, thank you, Mippa. Please continue with the 10th single, everyone.
Today was fun. It was delicious. It was delicious. Thank you, Suzu-chan.
Thank you for coming. Please continue to work with Suzu-chan, the Circuit Daimaou, after this.
Thank you very much. It was this way. I kept getting the camera wrong. This way? This way?
Thanks a lot. Bye-bye. Okay, I'm done. Oh, no, Tin-Tin swallowed it.
Bakun!